Haripriya Dogga

Cell: +918123939166

Email:haripriyasimc@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

High spirited marketer and advertising communications strategist transforming the way brands interact with audiences. With over 4+ years of experience at ecommerce startup, and an agency, brings a thoughtful perspective and blend of creative chops and digital data-savvy. Entrepreneurial at heart and a team player recognized for impassioned approach.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Advertising Specialist at Amazon, since April 2019

- Taking complete ownership for a portfolio of advertiser's accounts.
- Engaging with advertisers/in-country Account Manager to understand their advertising goals and expectations from the program.
- Analyzing account performance against key metrics to identify, recommend and implement
- Optimization solutions to increase efficiency and meet clients' KPIs.
- Analyzing data trends and creating keywords lists, bids and budget suggestions; gathering and analyzing data at account/campaign/industry level.
- Monitoring and communicating campaign progress through regular, in-depth activity reports and insights, using this knowledge as a basis for future campaigns.
- Working with Account Management, Sales & Marketing and Product teams to identify and solve issues blocking advertiser performance.
- Identifying opportunities to improve Amazon Advertising's product based on customer feedback, data analysis, and feature gaps with competitive products.

Account Manager – Solutions and Strategy at **Verbinden Communications**, from April 2018-Oct 2018

- Responsible for management of all phases of projects
- Defining project scope, goals, and deliverables to ensure consistency with company strategy and commitments
- Tracking key milestones and adjusting project plans accordingly
- Formulating risk management plans
- Coordinating multi-disciplinary project teams
- Oversee the daily activities of the team, including hiring and training new team members and evaluating the performance
- Conceptualizing events and branding the same.
- Destination marketing campaign ideation and execution.

Marketing Communications Manager at Play Games24x7 from July 2015 to February 2018

- Executed communication and marketing plans ensuring that a consistent 360 degrees' approach through all consumer touch points is in line with the Brand's point of view
- Ad making concept generation and its execution
- Managing website content
- Handled agencies in terms of campaign deliveries, idea execution
- Work with teams to understand client challenges and identify solutions
- Understanding player's life cycle to identify and fill product gaps, generate new ideas that improve user experience and drive growth.
- Strategy and management of all social media platforms
- Leverage video content to build ad-campaigns for multiple media channels
- Oversee, implement and manage weekly and seasonal editorial calendar

INTERNSHIP AT:

Client Servicing at Creative Media Pulse Technologies Ltd from April – July 2015

- Understanding Client requirement and come up with communication strategies
- Drafting client pitches and presentations
- Responsible to the client for on-time delivery of finished project
- Strategizing of communication collateral corporate brochures, outdoor, print etc.
- Creating communication pieces: emailers, newsletters, press releases

Media understanding at Lintas Media house, Bangalore from May2014 – July 2015

- Market research for clients in the organization from Media perspective
- Media understanding.

Social Media at Ashray Akruthi, Hyderabad from Oct- Nov 2014:

- Event Planning and Execution (World Disability Day)
- Created a manual for documenting the checklist of pre-event and post event
- Social Media Promotions

CERTIFICATIONS: Google AdWord certified

EDUCATION

- Completed MBA Branding and Public Relations from Symbiosis Institute of Media and Communication in 2015
- Completed Bachelor of Technology from Narayana engineering college (JNTU) in 2011

PERSONAL DETAILS

Languages known : English, Telugu, Hindi, Kannada, Tamil.

Date of Birth : 29-05-1990